For measuring user engagement, one option would be to survey students in
为了测量用户参与度 一种方法是对这门课程的学员进行调查
the course, asking how engaged they are, and use the survey responses as a proxy.
询问他们是如何参与的 将调查回应作为一个代替指标
This is option number 4.
这是方案 4
Another option would be to run a user experience study, and
另一个方案是进行用户体验研究
observe how students interact with the courses.
观察学员如何与课程互动
If you also asked the study participants how engaged they were,
如果你也询问他们的参与度如何
you could figure out whether their engagement correlates with something
你可以找出其参与度是否与更易于测量的信息相关
easier to measure, such as the length of time spent on the page or
如花费在页面上的时间长度
clicking more links to extra material.
或点击更多链接 查看更多资料
So, that's option number 2.
这是方案 2
Finally, since you think that course completion probably predicts engagement
最后 你认为完成课程可能意味着参与度很好
well, but is too hard to measure, you could also do a retrospective analysis
但这个很难测量 你也可以
of users who have completed courses and see what behaviors they have in common.
对完成课程的用户进行回顾性分析 看看他们共同的行为是什么
This is option number 5.
这是方案 5
Any two of these three would have been a good answer.
这三个中的任意两个都是很好的答案
You may also have thought of a good way to use one of the other techniques,
你也可以想出使用其他技巧的好方法
which is great as well.
这也很棒
The shopping site scenario is tricky.
购物网站的情况很棘手
One option would be to add some products and see how often the new pages were
一个可选方案是增加一些产品 看看这些新网页多久被访问一次
accessed, but that could be a significant investment for
但这可能是一笔很大的产品投资
products the users might not even be interested in.
用户不一定对这些产品感兴趣
Instead, you might want to use a focus group to get ideas from users
相反 你可能通过一个焦点小组 从用户那里了解
about what products they would like to see, or option 3.
他们期望看到什么产品 或方案 3
Alternatively, you could check if there is external data available from other
或者你可以检查是否能够从其他购物网站获得外部数据
shopping sites, indicating what users have wanted on those sites, or option 1.
表明了用户在这些网站上想要的产品是什么 或方案 1
For the ad viewing scenario, you might also consider external data, or
关于广告浏览的情况 你可能也会考虑外部数据或
option 1.
方案 1
Specifically, you could look for studies that show whether there's
特别是 你可以查看一些显示是否有可测量指标的研究
something you can measure, like time spent on the page or mouse hover events,
如花费在页面上的时间或鼠标悬浮的事件
that you could use as a proxy for whether the ad was viewed.
可以将这些指标作为广告是否被浏览过的代替指标
Or you could run a user experience study, option 2,
或者 你可以运行一个用户体验研究 选项 2
where you observe users, see what ads they're paying attention to with
你会观察用户 使用一个眼动跟踪相机看他们关注哪些广告
an eye-tracking camera, and then try to find a metric that correlates with that.
并试图找出一个与此相关的指标
You could also assume that clicks correlate with views and
你也可以假设点击量与浏览量相关
use your historical data to estimate that the relative number of clicks among
使用历史数据评估它在广告位上的
ad slots is a proxy for the relative views.
相对点击量 作为相对浏览量的一个代替指标
Or you could look at the lowest position where anyone has clicked and
或者你可以查看点击过的最低的位置
assume that people have read at least that far.
假设大家至少阅读到此处
Then, you could do a retrospective analysis of your data to see how well
然后对你的数据进行回顾性分析
these metrics would work.
看看这些指标的适用性如何
Again, any two of these three would have been a good answer, or
再强调一遍 这三个中的任意两个都会是很好的答案
maybe you thought of a way to use another technique.
或者 你可以想出使用另一种技巧的方法